class QuestionData {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> getAllQuestions() {
    return [
      {
        'id': 0,
        'question': 'In what year did the TV show The Walking Dead first air?',
        'true_answer': '2010',
        'options': [
          '2009',
          '2010',
          '2011',
          '2012',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 1,
        'question': 'In Season 1 of The Walking Dead, where is Rick trapped downtown?',
        'true_answer': 'Tank',
        'options': [
          'Car',
          'Home',
          'Tank',
          'WC',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 2,
        'question':
            'In Season 3 of The Walking Dead, how long did Michonne and Andrea survive on their own?',
        'true_answer': '8 months',
        'options': [
          '2 year',
          '1 month',
          '4 week',
          '8 months',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 3,
        'question': 'Which actor plays the character Glenn Rhee in The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Steven Yeun',
        'options': [
          'Steven Yeun',
          'Norman Reedus',
          'Andrew Lincoln',
          'Seth Gilliam',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 4,
        'question': 'Which actor plays Daryl on The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Steven Yeun',
        'options': [
          'Steven Yeun',
          'Norman Reedus',
          'Andrew Lincoln',
          'Seth Gilliam',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 5,
        'question': 'Which character is played by Sarah Wayne Callies in The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Lori Grimes',
        'options': [
          'Maggie Greene',
          'Beth Greene',
          'Carol Peletier',
          'Lori Grimes',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 6,
        'question':
            'In The Walking Dead, the Governor tells the Woodbury citizens they were betrayed by who?',
        'true_answer': 'Merle',
        'options': [
          'Merle',
          'Dary',
          'Andrea',
          'Michonne',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 7,
        'question': 'Who said the phrase "we dont kill the living"?',
        'true_answer': 'Rick Grimes',
        'options': [
          'Lori Grimes',
          'Rick Grimes',
          'Shane',
          'Dary Dixon',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 8,
        'question': "In The Walking Dead, Season 1, the color of the Sheriff's car is?",
        'true_answer': 'Blue & White',
        'options': [
          'White & White',
          'Green & White',
          'Black & White',
          'Blue & White',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 9,
        'question':
            "In The Walking Dead, who drops Merle's handcuff key and accidentally leaves him for the walkers?",
        'true_answer': 'T-Dog',
        'options': [
          'Glenn Rhee',
          'T-Dog',
          'Carl Grimes',
          'Rick Grimes',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 10,
        'question': 'In The Walking Dead, Season 1, who helped Rick first?',
        'true_answer': 'Morgan',
        'options': [
          'Morgan',
          'Glenn',
          'Daryl',
          'T-Dog',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 11,
        'question': "What was Glenn Rhee's job pre apocalypse in The Walking Dead?",
        'true_answer': 'Pizza Delivery',
        'options': [
          'Farmer',
          'Baseball Player',
          'Sherrif',
          'Pizza Delivery',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 12,
        'question': "Who is Beth Greene's dad in The Walking Dead?",
        'true_answer': 'Hershel',
        'options': [
          'Negan',
          'Rick',
          'Hershel',
          'Gregory',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 13,
        'question':
            'In Season 8 of The Walking Dead who do Rick, Maggie and Ezekiel rally their community in to war against?',
        'true_answer': 'Negan and the Saviors',
        'options': [
          'Negan and the Saviors',
          'The Commonwealth',
          'Oceanside',
          'Terminus',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 14,
        'question':
            'In The Walking Dead, what does Carl find in the upstairs bedroom of the house he and Rick stay in s04?',
        'true_answer': 'Video game system',
        'options': [
          'Video game system',
          'Comic book',
          'Walkers',
          'Dog',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 15,
        'question': 'In The Walking Dead, how does Rick go from the hospital to his house ?',
        'true_answer': 'By bicycle',
        'options': [
          'Horse',
          'Car',
          'By bicycle',
          'On Foot',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 16,
        'question': 'Who learns that they are pregnant in Season 2 of The Walking Dead ?',
        'true_answer': 'Lori',
        'options': [
          'Lori',
          'Carol',
          'Maggie',
          'Andrea',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 17,
        'question': "What is Michonne's primary weapon in The Walking Dead?",
        'true_answer': 'Katana',
        'options': [
          'Sniper Rifle',
          'Gun',
          'Knife',
          'Katana',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 18,
        'question': 'Who is Beth Greenes sister in The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Maggie',
        'options': [
          'Sofia',
          'Andrea',
          'Carol',
          'Maggie',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 19,
        'question': 'Who accidentally shoots Carl in Season 2 of The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Otis',
        'options': [
          'Shane',
          'Otis',
          'Hershel',
          'Morgan',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 20,
        'question': 'Who accidentally shoots Carl in Season 2 of The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Shane',
        'options': [
          'Shane',
          'Rick ',
          'Daryl',
          'T-Dog',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 21,
        'question':
            'What kind of car does Glenn steal and drive out of Atlanta in The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Dodge Challenger',
        'options': [
          'Chevrolet Corvette',
          'Ford Mustang',
          'Dodge Challenger',
          'Porshe',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 22,
        'question':
            'What do the survivors theorize most attracts walkers to humans on The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Smell',
        'options': [
          'Hate',
          'Speech',
          'Movement',
          'Smell',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 23,
        'question':
            'Season 1 of The Walking Dead takes place primarily en route to and from what major city?',
        'true_answer': 'Atlanta',
        'options': [
          'Atlanta',
          'Dallas',
          'New York',
          'Paris',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 24,
        'question':
            "In Season 1 of 'The Walking Dead', who is the leader of the survivors living in a nursing home in Atlanta?",
        'true_answer': 'Guillermo',
        'options': [
          'Andrew',
          'Guillermo',
          'Abulea',
          'Felipe',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 25,
        'question':
            ' In The Walking Dead, what does the Governor have that makes him think he can take the prison without firing a shot?',
        'true_answer': 'Michonne and Hershel',
        'options': [
          'A tank',
          'New Weapons',
          'Michonne and Hershel',
          'Heavy Armour',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 26,
        'question': 'Which of the following is not a character in The Walking Dead?',
        'true_answer': 'Maggie Rhee',
        'options': [
          'Bob Stookey',
          'Rick Grimes',
          'Beth Greene',
          'Maggie Rhee',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 27,
        'question':
            'In The Walking Dead, what does the Governor use to put down David after he turns into a walker?',
        'true_answer': 'Oxygen tank',
        'options': [
          'Oxygen tank',
          'Television',
          'Radio',
          'Revoler',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 28,
        'question': 'In The Walking Dead, what animal is Carl watching when he gets shot?',
        'true_answer': 'Deer',
        'options': [
          'Cow',
          'Wold',
          'Deer',
          'Eagle',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 29,
        'question': 'Around what was the Kingdom built?',
        'true_answer': 'School',
        'options': [
          'School',
          'Hospital',
          'Camping area',
          'Tennis Court',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 30,
        'question':
            'Who shows up on a horse to bring Lori to the Greene Family Farm after Carl is shot?',
        'true_answer': 'Maggie',
        'options': [
          'Beth',
          'Hershel',
          'Maggie',
          'Patricia',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 31,
        'question':
            "In which season did Rick say the phrase 'we tell ourselves we're the walking dead'?",
        'true_answer': '5',
        'options': [
          '3',
          '4',
          '5',
          '6',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 32,
        'question': 'Where did the story of season 3 take place?',
        'true_answer': 'Prison',
        'options': [
          'Alexandria',
          'Farm',
          'Prison',
          'Oceanside',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 33,
        'question': 'Where is Glenn from ?',
        'true_answer': 'Korea',
        'options': [
          'Japanese',
          'Chinese',
          'Korean',
          'Thai',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 34,
        'question': "What is the name of Negan's group?",
        'true_answer': 'Saviors',
        'options': [
          'Negan',
          'Thieves',
          'Saviors',
          'Negans',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 35,
        'question': '"You can breathe. You can blink. You can cry." sözleri kime aittir ?',
        'true_answer': 'Negan',
        'options': [
          'Governor',
          'Negan',
          'Rick',
          'Daryl',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 36,
        'question': 'What season does Rick go missing?',
        'true_answer': '9',
        'options': [
          '7',
          '8',
          '9',
          '10',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 37,
        'question': "Who does the phrase 'he killed glenn' belong to?",
        'true_answer': 'Maggie',
        'options': [
          'Daryl',
          'Carl',
          'Rick',
          'Maggie',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 38,
        'question': 'How many seasons did The Walking Dead series last?',
        'true_answer': '11',
        'options': [
          '13',
          '12',
          '11',
          '10',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 39,
        'question': 'In which season were Glenn and Abraham killed ?',
        'true_answer': '7',
        'options': [
          '5',
          '6',
          '7',
          '8',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 40,
        'question': 'What did Glenn find in the farm barn?',
        'true_answer': 'Walkers',
        'options': [
          'Walkers',
          'Cars',
          'Sofia',
          'Weaphones',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 41,
        'question':
            'The Sanctuary, which was the headquarters of the Saviors, was located in what abandoned facility?',
        'true_answer': 'a factory',
        'options': [
          'a prison',
          'a factory',
          'a school',
          'a farm',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 42,
        'question': "For Rick's group, the Greene Family Farm served as a base for which activity?",
        'true_answer': 'The search for Sophia',
        'options': [
          'For take',
          'For living',
          'To cure carl',
          'The search for Sophia',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 43,
        'question': 'In which state was the Hilltop located?',
        'true_answer': 'Virginia',
        'options': [
          'Virginia',
          'Georgia',
          'Carolina',
          'Alabama',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 44,
        'question':
            'Who shows up on a horse to bring Lori to the Greene Family Farm after Carl is shot?',
        'true_answer': 'Maggie',
        'options': [
          'Nobody',
          'Maggie',
          'Hershel',
          'Beth',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 45,
        'question': 'Who is the Governor of the Commonwealth?',
        'true_answer': 'Pamela Milton',
        'options': [
          'Pamela Milton',
          'Mercer',
          'Yumiko',
          'Daryl',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 46,
        'question': 'Who is the Governor of the Commonwealth?',
        'true_answer': 'Gregory',
        'options': [
          'Jesus',
          'Negan',
          'Gregory',
          'Maggie',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 47,
        'question': 'After the fall of the farm, he declared, "This is not a democracy anymore." ?',
        'true_answer': 'Rick Grimes',
        'options': [
          'Rick Grimes',
          'Dary Dixon',
          'Maggie Greene',
          'Glenn Rhee',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 48,
        'question': 'Eugene discovers the Commonwealth in his quest to meet what woman?',
        'true_answer': 'Stephanie',
        'options': [
          'Mercer',
          'Stephanie',
          'Pamela',
          'Leah',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 49,
        'question': 'Who kidnapped Glenn and Meggie?',
        'true_answer': 'Merle',
        'options': [
          'Gavernor',
          'Daryl',
          'Merle',
          'Negan',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 50,
        'question': 'How were Glenn and Abraham killed?',
        'true_answer': 'with baseball bat',
        'options': [
          'with a gun',
          'with baseball bat',
          'with a knife',
          'walker bite',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 51,
        'question': 'Who is our character who is not in the comic but is in the series?',
        'true_answer': 'Daryl',
        'options': [
          'Daryl',
          'Maggie',
          'Hershel',
          'Glenn',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 52,
        'question': 'What do our heroes find in the prison cafeteria?',
        'true_answer': 'Prisoners',
        'options': [
          'Prisoners',
          'Weaponry',
          'Health supplies',
          'Helicopter keys',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 53,
        'question': 'What is the name of our character who cannot speak?',
        'true_answer': '',
        'options': [
          'Yumiko',
          'Connie',
          'Sasha',
          'Magna',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 54,
        'question': 'Who is Carl being bitten trying to save?',
        'true_answer': 'Siddiq',
        'options': [
          'Aaron',
          'Yumiko',
          'Siddiq',
          'Daryl',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 55,
        'question': 'What is Carl sitting on the roof eating?',
        'true_answer': 'Pudding',
        'options': [
          'Cornflakes',
          'Dog Food',
          'Apple',
          'Pudding',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 56,
        'question': 'Who gave blood to Carl after he was shot?',
        'true_answer': 'Rick',
        'options': [
          'Glenn',
          'Rick',
          'Hershel',
          'Maggie',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 57,
        'question': 'Who healed Carl after he was shot ?',
        'true_answer': 'Hershel',
        'options': [
          'Maggie',
          'Beth',
          'Hershel',
          'Carol',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 58,
        'question':
            '"I want you to be someone who hates me rather than a dead person who loves me" To whom do these words belong?',
        'true_answer': 'Glenn',
        'options': [
          'Lori',
          'Maggie',
          'Glenn',
          'Carol',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 59,
        'question': 'Where did Sophia disappear ?',
        'true_answer': 'Highway',
        'options': [
          'Atlanta',
          'Farm',
          'Highway',
          'Terminate',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 60,
        'question': 'Who entered the well with the walker at the bottom ?',
        'true_answer': 'Glenn',
        'options': [
          'T-Dog',
          'Daryl',
          'Glenn',
          'Carl',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 61,
        'question': 'What were Glenn and Maggie going to town to buy?',
        'true_answer': 'Medicine',
        'options': [
          'Clothes',
          'Fuel',
          'Medicine',
          'Weapon',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 62,
        'question': 'Who killed Hershel?',
        'true_answer': 'Governor',
        'options': [
          'Walker',
          'Negan',
          'Governor',
          'by himself',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 63,
        'question': 'What is the name of the group that lives in the zombies?',
        'true_answer': 'Whisperers',
        'options': [
          'Alphas',
          'The deads',
          'Alexandria',
          'Whisperers',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 64,
        'question': "Which is not one of Rick Grimes' favorite weapons?",
        'true_answer': 'Baseball bat',
        'options': [
          'Ax',
          'Baseball bat',
          'Revolver',
          'Cleaver',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 65,
        'question': "In which season did Carl and the King's tiger die?",
        'true_answer': '8',
        'options': [
          '7',
          '8',
          '9',
          '10',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 66,
        'question':
            'What is the name of the prison that becomes a home for the survivors in Season 3 ?',
        'true_answer': 'West Georgia Correctional Facility',
        'options': [
          'The Sanctuary',
          'Woodbury',
          'The Farm',
          'West Georgia Correctional Facility',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 67,
        'question': 'Which character is known for riding a motorcycle?',
        'true_answer': 'Daryl Dixon',
        'options': [
          'Abraham Ford',
          'Eugene Porter',
          'Daryl Dixon',
          'Merle Dixon',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 68,
        'question':
            'Which character sacrifices themselves by blowing up a bridge to prevent a herd of walkers from attacking their community?',
        'true_answer': 'Rick Grimes',
        'options': [
          'Siddiq',
          'Rick Grimes',
          'Glenn Rhee',
          'Carl Grimes',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 69,
        'question': 'Which character cuts off his own arm to get rid of zombies?',
        'true_answer': 'Merle Dixon',
        'options': [
          'Merle Dixon',
          'Rick Grimes',
          'Aaron',
          'Hershel',
        ],
      },
      {
        'id': 70,
        'question': 'What pattern does Dary have on the back of his jacket?',
        'true_answer': 'Wings',
        'options': [
          'Wings',
          'Devil',
          'Skull',
          'Weapon',
        ],
      },
    ];
  }
}
